Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Cartoons/Collages, 1964, 1970-2008, undated; 20 Linear Feet in .5 record carton, 44 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 3 oversize flat folders, 1 flat-file folder
  - Reagan -- And I Love Peace, circa 1981-1989 (Box 104, Folder 70)
  - Reagan -- Murderer, circa 1981-1989 (Box 104, Folder 71)
  - Reagan -- Nuke Movie, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 72)
  - Reagan -- Real Men for Reagan, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 73)
  - Reagan -- Reagan in '84?, circa 1981-1989 (Box 104, Folder 74)
  - Reagan -- Mad to See Me, circa 1981-1989 (Box 104, Folder 75)
  - Reagan -- Liars Figure, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 76)
  - Reagan -- Solitary Vice, circa 1981-1989 (Box 104, Folder 77)
  - Reagan -- Kind, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 78)
  - Reagan -- Stay the Course, circa 1981-1989 (Box 104, Folder 79)
  - Reagan -- Kill One for the Gipper, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 80)
  - Reagan -- INA, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Reagan -- What, Me President, circa 1981-1989 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Reagan -- Vulnerability, circa 1981-1989 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Reagan -- Our Mistakes, circa 1982 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Reagan -- Brezhnev, circa 1981-1989 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Reagan -- Retire -- $100,000 Bonus, circa 1981-1989 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Not Repro'd, circa 1984 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Ring Around the Asshole, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Sayonara Sweeties, circa 1978 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Other Stages, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Fucking Replace TV, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - He Knew TS Eliot, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Anatomy Is Fate, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - It's Lonely At the Top, circa 1981-1989 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Truly Rich, circa 1981-1989 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Religion -- World God Forgot, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Religion -- Holy Mackerel School, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Religion -- Where's God?, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Religion -- O'Connor, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Religion -- Bishop, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Religion -- Lord is a Man of War, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Religion -- Adam and Eve, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Religion -- You Mean It's Not a Fountain, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Religion -- God Suicide, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Religion -- Weather, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - Religion -- Devil Made Me Do It, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - Religion -- New Pope, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Religion -- Jesus Sucks, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Religion -- It's a God, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Religion -- Jesus Saves, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 30)
  - Religion -- Pope, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 31)
  - Religion -- Armageddon, circa 1980-1990 (Box 105, Folder 32)
  - Religion -- God, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 33)
  - Religion -- Doesn't Look Jewish, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 34)
  - Religion -- Bomb in Gilead, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 35)
  - Religion -- God Loves Wars, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 36)
  - Religion -- Onward Xian Soldiers, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 37)
  - Religion -- Reincarnation, circa 1980-1999 (Box 105, Folder 38)
  - Religion -- God Rules! Ok?, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 39)
  - Religion -- God's Deodorant, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 40)
  - Religion -- Who Listens?, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 41)
  - Religion -- Adam the Wise, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 42)
  - Religion -- Obstructing Traffic, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 43)
  - Religion -- Moon, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 44)
  - Religion -- Bio of God, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 45)
  - Religion -- O Myself, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 46)
  - Religion -- Wasn't Commercial, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 47)
  - Religion -- Church and King, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 48)
  - Religion -- God Remembers Eden, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 49)
  - Religion -- What is God: A Circle?, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 50)
  - Religion -- Fuck 'im If He Can't Take a Joke, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 105, Folder 51)
  - Religion -- Chain Letter, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 52)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Better Than Shit Jokes, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 53)
  - 104 -- Stay Home, circa 1985-1994 (Box 105, Folder 54)
  - Last Day of Rest of Yr Life, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 55)
  - Too Old, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 56)
  - Seborrheic Keratosis, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 57)
  - The Old Fucks Get Heavy, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 58)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Liver Spot, 1989-1990 (Box 105, Folder 59)
  - Old and Stupid, circa 1985-1994 (Box 105, Folder 60)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Involuting, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 61)
  - Old Age is a Cliche, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 62)
  - I Shall Wear the Bottoms of My Condoms Rolled, circa 1985-1994 (Box 105, Folder 63)
  - Tough Getting Old, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 64)
  - Hope is Old, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 65)
  - Too Old -- Bush -- Script, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 66)
  - Bush Bills Prisoners, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 67)
  - Flags, 1981, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 68)
  - What Me Worry -- 5 Prez, 1991, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 69)
  - Get Ahead in America, circa 1985-1994 (Box 105, Folder 70)
  - America / China / Union of, circa 1985-1994 (Box 105, Folder 71)
  - CIA Kills, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 72)
  - Fuck -- Fuck, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 73)
  - America / King Philip, circa 1985-1994 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Can I Have a Pair?, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - President's Salmon, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Camels Fucks Baileys, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Why I Choose to Smoke, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Surgeon General Has Determined, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Up Shits Creek, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Zero Tolerance, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Coke Machine, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Fuckital, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Electric Cigs, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - A Long Way Baby, 1983, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Lungers, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Lech Morris, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Sellin' Death with Sex, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Phony Smokes From Cuba, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Ritz, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Do You Smoke?, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Philip Morris, circa 1985-1994 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Polk Award Long Island University Philip Morris, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Safe Dope, circa 1985-1994 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - For People Who Like to Choke, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Philip Morris Died, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - For People Who Like Freaks, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Smoking Problem, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Thinks of as a Pet, circa 1981 (Box 106, Folder 26)
  - Merit, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 27)
  - Aspirin, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 28)
  - Drug Abuse Pigs, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 29)
  - Cigs Fiends, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 30)
  - Religion -- Bangladesh Mon Amour, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 31)
  - Religion -- Conspiracy Theory, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - Religion -- Pierre Toussaint, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - Religion -- Old Fucks At Home -- 40,000 Dead in Iran, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - Religion -- Back in 5 Centuries, circa 1985-1994 (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - Religion -- X in Xmas, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 36)
  - Religion -- God on Welfare, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 37)
  - Religion -- Don't Like Yr Attitude, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 38)
  - Religion -- God is an Apostate, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 39)
  - Religion -- Hi God Got a Minute, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 40)
  - Religion -- Pissing on Your Foot, circa 1985-1994 (Box 106, Folder 41)
  - Religion -- Rotten People, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 42)
  - Religion -- Don't Be Petty, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 43)
  - Religion -- Gods Misery, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 44)
  - Religion -- Beware of Dog/God, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 45)
  - Religion -- Edit, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 46)
  - Religion -- Unwed Priests, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 47)
  - Religion -- God -- Don't Give Up Yr Day Job, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 48)
  - Religion -- God Must Have Hated the Common Man, circa 1985-1994 (Box 106, Folder 49)
  - Religion -- Wanna Ask God, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 50)
  - Religion -- Land God Remembered, 1986, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 51)
  - Religion -- Fuck and Get Fucked, 1990-1995 (Box 106, Folder 52)
  - Religion -- Banco Di Santo Spirito, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 53)
  - Religion -- Rapture, circa 1986 (Box 106, Folder 54)
  - Religion -- Cayce, 1984-1985 (Box 106, Folder 55)
  - Religion -- Tell God, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 56)
  - Religion -- Pope, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 57)
  - Religion -- League of Militant Agnostics, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 58)
  - Religion -- Difference Between Religion Patriotism, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 59)
  - Religion -- Gott Mitt Uns, 1984-1992 (Box 106, Folder 60)
  - Religion -- GMU (Gott Mit Uns), 1989-1999 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Religion -- Pope Up the Devils Ass, circa 1985-1994 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Religion -- St. Jude, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Religion -- Great Moments in History of Religion -- Popemobile, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Religion -- Tetra Shit, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Religion -- Shinto and Fighter, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Religion -- No Room at the Heaven for Muzhiks, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Gulf War -- Father of the Year, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Gulf War -- Iraq, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Gulf War -- Knife, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Gulf War -- All I Got Iraq Shirt, circa 1997 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Gulf War -- 1, 2, Many Nurembergs, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Gulf War -- They Show You the Dead Machines, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Gulf War -- Warcoholics, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Gulf War -- Iraq Fake Money, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Gulf War -- 40 Dead Instead, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Gulf War -- Gulf Bushdam, 1991, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - War -- WRL: Income Tax, 1992-1993 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - War -- Intrepid 2 and Nukeport, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - War -- No Atheists in Foxholes, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - War -- Maj. Turner, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - War -- Eat Who You Kill, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - War -- Kill in Good Health, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - War -- Junkie -- Vets, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - War -- Grumman and NR, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - War -- Frankie Frido, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - War -- Velly Good Yank, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - War -- Cong. Medal, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 28)
  - War -- Terror Hats, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - War -- Schwarzkopf's Book, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - War -- J's Can Kill Too, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 31)
  - War -- The Wave of the Future, circa 1985-1994 (Box 107, Folder 32)
  - War -- Burn 'Em, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 33)
  - War -- Russ -- Uke Dispute, 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - War -- War Fever, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - War -- Karl Kraus / War, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - War -- Draft, 1918, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - War -- Warverts, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - War -- Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Peacemaker, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - If At First...Decease, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Toy Marines, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - War -- CIA -- Puzzle, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - War -- Killer Lockheed, circa 1992 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - War -- Equal Opportunity Destroyer, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - War -- Salvador: Priests, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - War -- Weather, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - War -- Association of Defense Contractors, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - War -- Von Braun, 1987 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - War -- Star Wars, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - The Best Defense is..., circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - War -- Xmas at Pentagon, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - War -- Generic Unknown Soldier, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - War -- Vietnam Vets, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - War -- Great Moments in the History of the Media -- Iraq -- Turkey Shoot, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - War -- Fighter / Murderers, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - War -- Einstein on War, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - War -- My Country Right / Wrong, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - War -- Plowshares, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - War -- Killer Cards, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - War -- Weinberger Fighting for Peace, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - War -- F-16, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 28)
  - War -- As the World Burns, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 29)
  - War -- Recapping: 3 Serial Killers, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 30)
  - War -- Russ Weapons -- US, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 31)
  - War -- Killer Aircraft -- Carrier, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 32)
  - Jews -- Merchant of Tel Aviv, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 33)
  - Jews -- Alway Kill 1 U Love, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 34)
  - Jews -- Don't Make Trouble, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 35)
  - Jews -- Jericho, 1992, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 36)
  - Jews -- Never Born, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 37)
  - Jews -- Sharon, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 38)
  - Jews -- Arafat -- Rabin -- NY Post, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 39)
  - Jews -- Al Jolson, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 40)
  - Jews -- Lets Go to the Stoning, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 41)
  - Jews -- Stupid Kike Bastard, circa 1985-1994 (Box 108, Folder 42)
  - Jews -- Bush Raq, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 43)
  - Jews -- Jews Aren't Perfect, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 44)
  - Jews -- Jew Arab, 1985, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 45)
  - Jews -- First national Anthem, Cave 64, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Jews -- Nimrodi -- Little White House, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Jews -- Your Profession Has Destroyed Your Brain, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Jews -- Backwards Jewish Soldiers, 2004 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Jews -- Moscow Nights (When I Was a Young Man), 2004, 2008 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Jews -- What a Jew We Have in Jesus, or: The Four Insurgent Jews, 2007 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Jews -- 4 Jews, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Jews -- Cap and Com, 2000 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Jews -- Right to Arm Bears, 2008 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Jews -- Onions and Garlic, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Jews -- Jewish Pets, 1997, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Jews -- Moshiach!, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Jews -- Wailing Wall, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Jews -- Abortion: PhD, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Jews -- Bombucracy, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Jews -- Halutzi Kaputzi, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Jews -- Brit Museum, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Thatcher, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Queenie, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Jews -- Good for Jews, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Bleeding Heart, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Mideast Terrorists, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Israeli Psychologists, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Little Pig Sausages, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - It's a Goy, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Wine is a Mocker, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Is That Enough?, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Reichmanns, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - Shamir Govt, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Auschwitz -- Arbeit Macht Frei, circa 1985-1994 (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - On the Banks of the Swiss, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - They All Are Jews, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - Life/Death is Funny, 1999 (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Schindler's List, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Jew Miscellany and Vanunu, 1991-1999 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Israeli Armenians Arab, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Fucking Politics, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Rassenhass, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Matzo -- Ball Soup, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - I Live in De Back, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Jews -- Aids, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Rudolph Brown -- Nose Nazi, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Last of the Red Hot Roothless Cosmopolitans, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Sperm a Good Idea, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - German Inflation, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Old Farts At Home -- Anti..Sem -- Zionism, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Rude Man, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Foreskin of Xrist, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - It Should've Been Irving, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Minsk -- Pinsk, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Cross Dressing, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Rootless Cosmopolitans, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Kill Ayesha?, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Pearl Shits, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Bush the Aviator, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Diana, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - History Will Show Our Stupidity, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - JP Morgas Ass, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - Wargasm NASA, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Patrick Henry, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Armaments Fair, 2003, 2007 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - An Oldie But Goldie, 2008 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Book of Perverbs -- A Penny Earned, 2008 (Box 110, Folder 30)
  - Grosz, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Ass Tuli, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - Picasso's Pussy, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - One My-Nyut Play, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 34)
  - Steady Work, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 35)
  - Banker and Boss, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 36)
  - Salute to the Nuclear Age, circa 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 37)
  - Words Written in Wine, 2008 (Box 110, Folder 38)
  - Is Amerika A Fraud, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Do You Do Sex, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Condoms, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Norton's Folly, 2000 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - State of the Union, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - 31 Gun Salute to the Military, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Globalization, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - NY Times, 1983-1996 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Safire / Kent State, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- The Paper for Suits By Suits, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Poor Baby -- Tritium, 1990 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Good Break on Wages, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - All News Fit to Print, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Fit to Print, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Corrections NY Times, 1988-1994 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Rosenthal, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Fucking NY Times, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Farting / Non Farting, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Sulzberger, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Daily Glut, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - US -- Them, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Our We USA Today, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Incest, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Rich or Poor...Good to Have Money, circa 1985-1994 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Every Little Movement, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - TV Critics, circa 1984-1990 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Murdgate, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Murdoch 1, 1987, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - Murdoch 2, 1994-1996 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Media -- Jargon, 1983, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Nobody's Reporting, circa 1984-2004 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - School as Prison, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Whaya Mean No Free Speech? NY Times Rates, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Invent a Disease, 2006 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Art Young Whore House, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- CIA Works for Times, circa 1984-1995 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - The American Press, 2004 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Cable TV News "Mine is Proper", 2007 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Big News Tonight, circa 1983 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- 9 Spot Illustrations for the New Yorker, 1988, 1994, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Freedom of the Press, circa 1985-1995 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Karl Kraus How Wars Start, circa 1985-1995 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Mastermurdoch, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - A Kid Again, circa 1985-2000 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Every Little Meaning, 1993 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - 21 -- Gun Salute to Journalism, circa 1985-2000 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - The Presstitutes, 2007 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Joann Wypijewski, undated (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Xian Sex, circa 1985-2007 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Black Ducks, undated (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Minister Beats Boy, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Sleep w John?, undated (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Mrs. Ben Lux, circa 1984-2000 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - No Cocks or Cunts, 1994, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Daumier, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Fuck Obscenity, circa 1984-2000s (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Censorship, 1991-2000 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - In this Cartoon, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - I'm Looking for a Job, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Eyes on the Prize, 1993-1994 (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - Spielberg / Schindler, circa 1993 (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - E.T., circa 1980s-1990s (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - Carlin Romano The Nation "Listens"..., 2002 (Box 112, Folder 33)
  - Poem for Censors, undated (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Kiss Editors Ass, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 35)
  - Book of Perverbs -- What the Hell Was That?, 2007 (Box 112, Folder 36)
  - Poetry Mines, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 37)
  - Sklar / Huffington, 2006 (Box 112, Folder 38)
  - September Morn, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 39)
  - Write Childrens Books, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 40)
  - Paper and Poetry, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 41)
  - Rare Book School, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 42)
  - Old Farts At Home -- Too Many Books, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 43)
  - First Thought Best Thought, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 44)
  - What Do You Expect To Accomplish By This Cartoon?, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 45)
  - George Grosz, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 46)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Niche "Gone", 1994 (Box 112, Folder 47)
  - Ford Times, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 48)
  - Newsqueak, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 49)
  - What Happens to News, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 50)
  - Five Star Final, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 112, Folder 51)
  - Use Shithouse?, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 52)
  - Psychol Today, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 53)
  - Vanity Fair, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 54)
  - Jewish Peace Fellowship and Making Many Book, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Opto, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Poor Richard, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Book Doctor, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Not in Who's Who, 1996 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - NY Post Cartoon, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- London Times, Dirk, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- What's New?, 1991, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Media -- Shit Harvard, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Clint -- Mast, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - 5 Separate Publishers, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Cockburn -- USA Today, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Best Head of the Year, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Faltering Times, 1985 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - TV Guide Network, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Vanity Fair 1, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Cobblestones, 1985 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Eat Shit, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - In These Times, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- Stop the Presses, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 20)